(Sheldon:)Oh, no, they went
back down!
(Raj:)All right, guys, what game
do you want to play?
(Howard:)Let's see.
(Howard:)How about
"Emily or Cinnamon?"
(Raj:)You know what? I think
it's a little weird
(Raj:)that you remember me
saying all these things.
(Raj:)Maybe the truth is-- you're
jealous of all my relationships.
(Howard:)Oh, maybe I am.
(Howard:)Who wouldn't want
to be the girl,
(Howard:)or possibly dog,
to hear the words:
"You're so lucky.
(Howard:)You have the
shiniest hair."
(Leonard:)That is a tough one.
Uh, I-I know he brushes
both of them.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen...
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)I have figured out the perfect
way for you to irritate me.
(Sheldon:)I'd like you to be my
intellectual sparring partners.
(Sheldon:)From now on,
when I make an assertion,
(Sheldon:)I need you to challenge it.
(Leonard:)So you just want us to disagree
with whatever you say?
(Sheldon:)Yes.